As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's case involves three siblings! Mysteries upon mysteries!
!تتضمن قضيّة اليوم ثلاثة أشقّاء! ألغاز تلفّها ألغاز
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Ugh! And I came all this way because he said it was a big incident...
يا إلهي، قطعتُ الطريق لهذا المكان ...لأنّه قال أنّها حادثة كبيرة
You should've just taken the case!
كان عليك قبول القضيّة
Yeah, right! I'm not gonna search for some lousy missing iguana!
!حمقاء! لن أبحث عن حيوانٍ زاحف
Sounds perfect for you...
...أراه عملاً ملائماً لك
What seems to be the matter?
أهناك مشكلة؟
My car broke down on me. Could I ask for a lift to my villa up ahead?
تعطّلت سيّارتي، هلّا أخذتني لمنزلي الجبلي في الطريق أمامنا من فضلك؟
I'll compensate you, of course.
سأجازيك بالطبع
I'd be glad to give you a lift!
!سأقلّك بكلّ سرور
Thank you. My name is Hotta.
شكراً لك، اسمي هوتّا
It's nice to meet you!
سُررت بلقائك
H-Hotta Industries!
!شـ-شركة هوتّا للصناعات
You run that huge corporation?!
!أنت رئيس تلك الشركة الكبيرة؟
Hey, Yamauchi.
!ياماوتشي
S-Sir!
!سـ-سيّدي
What happened?!
ماذا حصل؟
My car broke down. These folks gave me a ride.
تعطّلت سيّارتي، فأقلّني هذا السيّد
Is that so? I'm Yamauchi, the caretaker of this villa.
هكذا إذاً، أنا مُدبّر هذا المنزل الجبلي، أُدعى ياماوتشي
Thank you for helping him.
شكراً لمساعدتك الرئيس
It's nothing! I'm sure he would've done the same!
لم يكن شيئاً يُذكر، علينا مساعدة بعضنا عند الحاجة
Are Koichi and the others already here?
هل وصل كويتشي والبقيّة؟
Yes. Everyone is worried because you're late.
أجل، الجميع قلقون من تأخّرك
I wonder. I bet they hope I died in an accident...
أشكّ في ذلك، إنّهم يتمنّون موتي في حادثٍ بالتأكيد
Say, Mori-san. Tonight is my birthday party.
بالمناسبة يا موري-سان، اليوم موعد حفلة عيد ميلادي
I'd like to invite you, as thanks...
أودّ دعوتك تعبيراً عن امتناني
Oh, but...
...لكن
You don't mind, do you?
لا تمانع، صحيح؟
Don't mind if I do!
!سأقبل عرضك
You didn't arrive on time, Father, so we were worried
...لم تصل في الوقت يا أبي فشعرنا بالقلق
you had gotten in an accident along the way.
من تعرّضك لحادثٍ في الطريق
Yes! Hotta Industries is nothing without you, Father!
أجل، فلا تساوي شركة هوتّا للصناعات شيئاً دونك
For sure! The company needs you to stay well for a long time to come!
بالفعل، لا زالت الشركة بحاجة لك لوقتٍ طويل
Chateau Petrus, 1979. From Koichi-sama.
شاتو بيتروس، 1979. هديّة من كويتشي-ساما
Hey. Is that expensive wine?
أذاك نبيذ باهظ؟
Yes. Eye-poppingly expensive.
أجل، لحدٍّ يخرج عينيك
It's the king of red wine!
يدعونه بملك النبيذ الأحمر
Now then, let us toast to Father's 58th birthday.
لنشرب إذاً نخب عيد ميلاد أبينا الثامن والخمسين
Hold it!
!انتظروا
Why don't you drink first, big brother?
لمَ لا تشرب أنت أوّلاً يا أخي؟
What is that supposed to mean?!
ما قصدك؟
Just figured it wouldn't be funny if there was poison in it...
خطر لي أنّه لن يكون مسليّاً وجود سمٍّ فيه
How rude, Ryoji-san!
!يا للفظاظة يا ريوجي-سان
I've heard the rumors.
وصلتني الشائعات
The overseas branch has taken big hits because of your poor forecasts.
تلقّى الفرع خارج البلاد أضرار كبيرة بسبب توقّعاتك الخاطئة
And I hear you're going to be dismissed and sent to a subsidiary.
وسمعتُ أنّك ستُصرف وتُنقل لشركة فرعية
You're suggesting I'm planning to kill Father over that?!
!تظنني سأقتل أبي لهذا؟
I hear you've racked up some heavy-duty gambling debts lately!
!أنت من شاع أنّه دخل قمارات كبيرة وغرق في الديون
M-Mind your own business!
!لا-لا تتدخل فيما لا يخصّك
Enough!
!يكفي
My dinner...
...عشائي
I've had just about enough of this!
!ضقتُ ذرعاً بهذا
I see my brothers are as close as ever.
لا يزال شقيقاي مقرّبين كعادتهما
Sis!
!أختي
Eldest Daughter- Hotta Fumiko (30)
(30) هوتّا فوميكو الابنة الكبرى
Fumiko!
!فوميكو
Why are you here?
لمَ أنتِ هنا؟
What a harsh hello, after sending an invitation yourself.
يا للتحيّة القاسية، بعدما أرسلت الدعوة بنفسك
We severed all ties five years ago! I'd never send you an invitation!
!قطعت العلاقة بك قبل 5 أعوام !يستحيل أن أرسل لك دعوة
I don't want to see your face! Get out!
!لا أريد رؤية وجهك! اخرجي
You're the one who called me here to tell me something!
أنت من استدعاني وقال أنّ لديه !موضوعاً يريد الكلام فيه معي
I have nothing to say to you!
!لا أريد الكلام معك بشيء
Tonight was supposed to be a feast, too...
كان يُفترض أن نأكل وليمةً اليوم
Oh, Dad.
...أبي
Say, what happened between Hotta-san and Fumiko-san?
ماذا حصل بين هوتّا-سان وفوميكو-سان في الماضي؟
Good question. I've only been their caretaker for two years,
لا أدري، مضى عامان فقط على كوني مدبّر المنزل
so I don't know what happened long ago.
فلا أعرف الماضي
Whiskey, huh? Whose present is this?
ويسكي؟ هدية من؟
W-W-What the--
!ما-ماذا حصل؟
S-Sir!
!سـ-سيّدي
A bomb...
...قنبلة
W-What the--
...ما-ما هذا
Call the police!
!اتّصل بالشرطة
R-Right!
!حـ-حاضر
Looks like I can assume a bomb was planted in here.
يبدو أنّ قنبلةً زُرعت في هذه الغرفة
That's absurd!
!هذه سخافة
Stay out! Please wait outside until the police arrive!
لا تدخلوا! انتظروا خارجاً حتّى وصول الشرطة رجاءً
And just who are you?!
!من أنت لتتصرف بهذا التعالي؟
The world's greatest detective, Mori Kogoro!
!أعظم متحرٍّ على الأرض، موري كوغورو
Mori Kogoro?!
!موري كوغورو؟
The famous detective?!
ذاك المتحرّي الشهير؟
This was dynamite...
كان ديناميت
Doesn't smell like dynamite to me.
رائحته لا تبدو رائحة ديناميت لي
Trying to butt in again, huh?!
!تقحم أنفك مُجدداً؟
He has wood and glass fragments in him!
به شظايا خشب وزجاج
Stupid kid! Oww!
!أيّها الشقيّ! مؤلم
This is a whiskey display box!
!هذا... صندوق تقديم ويسكي
Ah! The glass stuck in him is from a bottle!
فهمت، الزجاج العالق به كان من قنّينة
What's that?
ما هذا؟
The bomb was inside the whiskey box!
!كانت القنبلة داخل صندوق ويسكي
That's why there are fragments all over Hotta-san's body!
!لذا تملأ الشظايا جثّة هوتّا-سان
I see--
...فهمت
I don't need you to tell me! I realized that long before you!
أدركتُ هذا قبل وقت طويل !دون أن أحتاجك لتخبرني
Yeesh...
...يا إلهي
Dirt? What's it doing in here?
تراب؟ لمَ موجود في الغرفة؟
Dad!
أبي
Where's Yamauchi-san?
أين ياماوتشي-تشان؟
He says the phone is out...
قال أنّ الهاتف مقطوع
Say what?!
!ماذا؟
If anyone here holds a grudge against Father... it's you, Fumiko!
إذا كان هناك شخصٌ بيننا يكنّ ضغينةً لأبي... فهي أنت يا فوميكو
Yeah! You hadn't spoken in five years!
!صحيح! لم تتكلّما لخمسة أعوام
Suddenly showing up now without an invitation is undeniably strange!
!ظهورك المُفاجئ بلا دعوة غريبٌ قطعاً
Yes. I did hate him. Enough to want to kill him!
!أجل، كنتُ أبغضه بالفعل... بما يكفي لقتله
But I didn't do it. Though I do thank whoever did.
لكني لم أفعل، رغم أنّي أريد شكر من فعل
I assume you all feel the same.
أظنّكما تشاركانني مشاعري
What horrible siblings...
يا للأشقّاء الفظيعين
How are the phone lines?!
كيف كانت خطوط الهاتف؟
They've been cut by a knife or something...
بدا أنّها قُطعت بسكّين
A knife?!
بسكّين؟
What should we do, Mori-san?
ما العمل يا موري-سان؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
The bomb was planted inside a whiskey box.
زُرِعت القنبلة داخل صندوق ويسكي
You recognize it?!
!أتعرفه؟
Well...
...في الواقع
Out with it!
!أخبرنا
I believe it was a present Ryoji-sama gave to him...
أظنّه كان هديّةً من ريوجي-ساما للسيّد
I remember because I took it to his room.
أتذكّر لأنّي أخذته لغرفته
R- Ryoji did it?!
ر-ريوجي كان الفاعل؟
Say, where is Ryoji-san?!
أين ريوجي-سان بالمناسبة؟
He ran off...
...هرب
That can't be!
لا يمكن
A knife!
!سكّين
This is Ryoji-sama's car.
هذه سيّارة ريوجي-ساما
He hasn't gotten far, if he left his car behind...
لا يمكن أنّه ابتعد بتركه لسيّارته
Eh? Does that mean he's still lurking about?!
أيعني هذا أنّه لا يزال في الأرجاء؟
What's this?! It's been slashed!
!هذا... مُزّق الإطار
Mori-san. What do we do now?
موري-سان، ماذا نفعل الآن؟
It's probably best to leave in our cars.
يجدر بنا المغادرة في سيّاراتنا
Not an option.
ذلك ليس ممكناً
What?!
!ماذا؟
All four of these cars have slashed tires.
مُزّقت إطارات السيّارات، الأربع كلّها
What?! Does that mean we can't leave this villa?!
!لا يُعقل! لا يمكننا مغادرة المنزل إذاً؟
Ryoji did this. There's rubber stuck on his knife!
كانت فعلة ريوجي، يوجد مطّاط عالق بالسكّين
How did you get here?
كيف وصلتما هنا؟
We can't drive, so we took a limo...
لا يمكننا القيادة فاستقللنا سيّارة خاصّة
Are there any other cars?
أتوجد سيّارات أخرى؟
There's my car. But it's broken and hardly in a usable state...
توجد سيّارتي، لكنّها معطّلة وليست صالحة للقيادة
Say, if Ryoji-san is the killer, why would he slash his own tires?
إذا كان ريوجي-سان الفاعل فلمَ مزّق إطارات سيّارته أيضاً؟
Isn't it obvious? If his tires were the only ones not slashed,
،أليس واضحاً؟ إن كانت إطاراته الوحيدة السليمة
the police would suspect him right off the bat.
ستشتبه به الشرطة فوراً
That's strange. He would still be suspected right off the bat
هذا غريب، سيظلّ المشبوه به الأول إذا انفجر الويسكي الذي أرسله
if his whiskey exploded and he disappeared right after!
ثم اختفى فجأةً بعدها، حتّى بعد هذه الحيلة
Ryoji-san didn't do this.
لم يكن ريوجي-سان الفاعل
But if the killer's goal was actually to trap everyone inside this villa...
...لكن إذا كان هدف القاتل احتجاز الجميع في المنزل
...something else might happen!
!قد يحصل شيءٌ آخر
In any event, Ryoji-san is still lurking around here.
بأيّ حال، لا يزال ريوجي في الأرجاء
Make sure to stay together and not go off alone!
احرصوا على البقاء مُتقاربين وعدم التصرّف وحدكم
Screw that! I'm going back to my room!
!لا تمازحني! سأذهب لغرفتي
Geez, right after I warn her...
يا إلهي، بعدما حذرتها فوراً
Let us all go back inside.
حسناً، لنرجع للداخل يا سادة
Right...
أجل
Mori-san. I'll try to fix my car...
موري-سان، سأحاول إصلاح سيّارتي
Be extremely careful.
توخّ أشدّ الحذر
Hey, kid! Let's go!
!ولد! سنرجع
Okay!
حسناً
Fumiko-san's pendant...
قلادة فوميكو-سان
Fumiko-san.
فوميكو-سان
Quiet! I'm busy right now!
!اصمت! أنا مشغولة الآن
Are you looking for this?
أتبحثين عن هذه؟
Give that back!
!أعدها
Thanks, little boy. This is the most important thing to me.
شكراً لك يا فتى، هذه أغلى شيءٍ عليّ
Is that your lover?
حبيبك؟
He died, five years ago. Suicide-- no, it was more like murder.
...مات قبل خمسة أعوام، انتحار كلا، كان كأنّه تعرّض للقتل
By Hotta Kosaku, my father!
!من قِبل أبي، هوتّا كوساكو
That's why I left. I couldn't forgive my father...
لذا غادرتُ البيت، لم أستطع مسامحة أبي
Oh, I'm sorry. I guess there's no point in telling this to a little kid...
آسفة، لا جدوى من إخبار هذا لفتى صغير
Fumiko-san held a grudge against Hotta-san.
كانت فوميكو-سان تكنّ ضغينةً لهوتّا-سان
But did she have a chance to plant the bomb in the whiskey box?
لكن هل كان لديها فرصة زرع القنبلة بصندوق الويسكي؟
What's this?!
...هذا
Chemical Fertilizer
سماد كيميائي
Chemical fertilizer! Could that bomb have been...
...سماد كيميائي؟ أيمكن أنّ القنبلة كانت
Just as I thought!
كما ظننت
Sulfur
كبريت
Sulfur and chemicals! And that chemical fertilizer!
كبريت ومواد كيميائية، كما ذاك السماد الكيميائي
No doubt about it! That person is the killer!
!لا شكّ في الأمر، القاتل هو ذاك الشخص
This person is--!
...هذا الشخص
Is it fixed?
هل أصلحتها؟
That car sure is old!
إنّها سيّارة قديمة بالفعل
It's the first one I ever designed.
كانت أوّل سيّارة صممتُها
You were a car designer?
كنت مصمّم سيّارات؟
Yes, until five years ago.
أجل، حتّى قبل خمسة أعوام
I quit after something happened...
استقلتُ بعد حادثة
I've never seen a car like this before!
!أوّل مرّة أرى سيّارة كهذه
Huh? It's an old-style car, but it has an airbag...
...ماذا؟ إنّها سيّارة قديمة الطراز لكن بها كيس هوائي
Uhh, Conan-kun, could you go get Fumiko-san?
كونان-كن، هلّا ناديت فوميكو-سان؟
What for?
لمَ؟
To get the police. Everyone feels uneasy with just Mori-san, right?
لاستدعاء الشرطة، الجميع يشعرون بالقلق بوجود موري-سان وحده، صحيح؟
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
I'm the caretaker. I have a responsibility to stay here.
أنا المدبّر، أحمل مسؤولية البقاء هنا
Okay!
!فهمت
Ah, time for food!
!وقت الطعام
Where's Conan-kun?
أين كونان-كن؟
Probably off playing somewhere.
يلعب في مكانٍ ما غالباً
What a lost cause. I'll go find him.
لا مفرّ، سأذهب للبحث عنه
My food...
...طعامي
There's no need to be shocked. This photograph was in your room.
لا حاجة لأن تُصدم، فقد كانت الصورة في غرفتك
You went into my room without permission?!
أدخلت غرفتي بلا إذن؟
I found something interesting in there...
وجدتُ أشياء مثيرة للاهتمام هناك
Sulfur and other chemicals, hidden inside a cabinet.
كبريت ومواد كيميائية أخرى مخبّأة في خزانة
The explosive wasn't dynamite. It was a homemade bomb
لم يكن الانفجار بفعل ديناميت، بل قنبلة معدّة يدوياً
made of chemical fertilizer, sulfur, and other chemicals!
!من سماد كيميائي وكبريت ومواد كيميائية أخرى
You can make a bomb out of that?!
يمكنك صنع قنبلة من أشياء كهذه؟
Indeed, you can.
أجل
If mixed properly, it can produce an explosive as powerful as dynamite.
إن مزجتها بطريقة ما، يمكنها إنتاج انفجار لا يقلّ قوّةً عن الديناميت
Ridiculous! Why would I want to kill the master of the house?!
!سخافة! لمَ قد أقتل سيّد المنزل؟
This incident was entirely to avenge the person in that photograph.
كانت هذه الحادثة انتقاماً للشخص في الصورة
Hotta-san drove him to suicide five years ago.
دفعه هوتّا-سان للإقدام على الانتحار قبل 5 أعوام
And he was your son, Yamauchi-san.
وكان ابنك يا ياماوتشي-سان
You were the one who took Ryoji-san's whiskey
كنتَ من أخذ الويسكي الذي جلبه ريوجي-سان
and delivered it to Hotta-san's room.
وأوصله لغرفة هوتّا-سان
That's when you placed the homemade explosive inside the box,
وضعت آنذاك القنبلة يدوية الصنع داخل الصندوق
an igniter under the lid,
أضفت مُشعِلاً تحت الغطاء
and easily-ignited phosphorous in the bomb.
كما فسفوراً سريع الاشتعال في القنبلة
It was basically like striking a match.
كان الأمر أشبه بإشعال عود ثقاب
But it wasn't meant to be a perfect crime.
لكن لم يُفترض أن تكون جريمةً مثالية
Because you needed to distance yourself from suspicion
فقد كنتَ بحاجة لإبعاد نفسك عن الشبهة
until your next crime.
حتّى جريمتك التالية
His next crime?
جريمته التالية؟
Fumiko-san?
فوميكو-سان؟
Well done, Mori-san. It is just as you say.
كما يُتوقع منك يا موري-سان، الأمر كما استنتجته
My son Kentaro was an extraordinary pianist with a bright future.
كان ابني كينتارو عازف بيانو موهوب بمستقبل لامع
He had dated a girl for a long time, but because of his paltry income,
واعد فتاةً أحبّها لوقت طويل، لكن لم يستطع التقدّم لخطبتها
he was unable to propose to her.
بسبب دخله الماليّ الضئيل
But five years ago, he won a competition and finally earned appraisal.
لكنّه فاز بإحدى المسابقات قبل 5 أعوام ونال الاعتراف بموهبته أخيراً
And then Kentaro proposed to her. But...
...ثمّ تقدّم كينتارو لخطبة تلك الفتاة، لكن
...the woman's father-- Hotta-san-- was against it.
عارض والد الفتاة الزواج، أي هوتّا-سان
S-So that woman was Fumiko-san?!
كـ-كانت تلك الفتاة فوميكو-سان إذاً؟
Kentaro met with Hotta to get permission to marry her.
ذهب كينتارو لمقابلة هوتّا لأخذ قبوله بالزواج
But Hotta not only refused, but he ruined Kentaro's fingers as well!
لكن لم يرفض هوتّا فحسب، بل سحق أصابعه أيضاً
The piano was Kentaro's life! And he had it stolen away forever!
!كان البيانو حياة كينتارو! وسرقها للأبد
What's more, the woman ran off, leaving him behind devastated!
!كما رحلت تلك المرأة وتركته مكسوراً
So the poor boy...
...لذا المسكين
Upon learning all of this after his funeral, I was shocked to realize
بعدما عرفت كلّ هذا في جنازته، تملّكتني الصدمة
that as a company man, I had known nothing about my own son...
فقد جهلت حياة ابني تماماً وأنا موظّف شركة
And that's why you decided to get revenge...
لذا قرّرت الأخذ بثأره
Yes. After quitting the company, I investigated Hotta
أجل، تحرّيتُ أمر هوتّا بعد الاستقالة
and became his caretaker to find a chance to exact revenge.
وأصبحت مدبّر منزله الجبلي لأحصل على فرصة الانتقام
But Fumiko had left the family, and it took me two years to locate her.
،لكنّ فوميكو كانت قد تركت العائلة فاحتجت عامين لتحديد مكانها
Then you chose Hotta-san's birthday party as the stage for revenge
ثمّ اخترت حفلة عيد ميلاد هوتّا-سان مسرحاً للانتقام
and sent Fumiko-san an invitation.
وأرسلت الدعوة لفوميكو-سان
Yes. Now I will have no regrets in life.
أجل، لا ندم في حياتي الآن
But Fumiko-san is safe and sound in the car--
لكنّ فوميكو-سان بأمان في السيّارة
The moment I got her to step into that car, my revenge succeeded.
تحقّق انتقامي حال دخولها السيّارة
There's a trap in the car, you see.
فهناك فخّ بها
The airbag is set to go off when she steps hard on the brakes.
كيس الهواء معدّ بحيث يخرج عندما تضغط بقوّة على المكابح
As we speak, she's probably...
...إنّها غالباً الآن
You really don't know anything, do you?
أنتَ جاهل حقاً
Why do you think Fumiko-san is still single, after all this time?
لمَ لا تزال فوميكو-سان عزباء للآن برأيك؟
Because even now, she continues to love Kentaro-san!
!لأنّها لا تزال تُحب كينتارو-سان
Absurd! A rude woman disowned by her father would never do that!
سخافة! امرأة وقحة تبرّأ منها أباها !لن تقوم بذلك أبداً
She wasn't disowned! She left on her own!
!لم يتبرّأ منها! غادرت البيت من تلقاء نفسها
She couldn't forgive her father for what he did to Kentaro-san!
لم تستطع مسامحة أبيها على ما فعله بكينتارو-سان
That's a lie! It's nonsense!
!هذه كذبة! هراء
She abandoned Kentaro!
!لقد تخلّت عن كينتارو
What's this?
ما هذه؟
That's Fumiko-san's treasure.
إنّها كنز فوميكو-سان
A treasure chest filled with her memories with Kentaro-san,
كنز مليء بذكرياتها عن كينتارو-سان
and her feelings for him.
ومشاعرها له
Fumiko-san always wears it at all times.
كانت فوميكو-سان ترتديه طوال الوقت
Even now, Kentaro-san is the dearest person to her, Yamauchi-san!
!لا تزال ترى كينتارو-سان أغلى شخص لديها يا ياماوتشي-سان
W-What have I done?!
ما... ما الذي فعلتُه؟
I've killed the person who loved my son that much!
...قتلتُ الشخص الذي أحبّ ابني لهذه الدرجة
Fumiko-san! Didn't the airbag deploy?!
فوميكو-سان؟ لم يخرج كيس الهواء؟
No. Mori-san had Conan-kun tell me to come back right away...
كلا، طلب موري-سان من كونان-كن أن يخبرني بالعودة فوراً
Fumiko-san... I'm...
...فوميكو-سان، أنا
I hated my father, too. Enough to want to kill him.
كنتُ أبغض أبي، لحدّ رغبتي بقتله
But I can't forgive Kentaro-san, either.
لكنّي لا أستطيع مسامحة كينتارو-سان أيضاً
He left me all alone... And drove his own father to do this...
...فقد تركني بمفردي، ودفع أبيه لفعل هذا
He really is sinful...
...إنّه آثم حقاً
Ryoji-san had been locked up in the basement.
كان ريوجي-سان محبوساً في القبو
Oww!
!مؤلم
Huh?! Where did everyone go?!
ماذا؟ أين ذهب الجميع؟
Man, I'm hungry. Oh, that's right! We're about to have breakfast!
...أشعر بالجوع
Yamauchi-san! Breakfast, please!
!ياماوتشي-سان! الإفطار من فضلك
I'm so hungry I could die! Anything'll do, just please hurry!
!الجوع يقتلني! لا أمانع أيّ شيء، أسرع وحسب رجاءً
Yamauchi-san!
!ياماوتشي-سان
Dad!
!أبي
It's strange! Something isn't right!
غريب، هناك أمرٌ ليس في محلّه
That's weird.
يا للغرابة
You're supposed to wash makeup off before applying a face pack!
تغسل مساحيق التجميل قبل وضع قناع الوجه عادةً
T-That's it! That person really is the killer!
فـ-فهمت! ذاك الشخص هو القاتل بالفعل إذاً
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Face Pack Murder Case."
جريمة قتل قناع الوجه
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Lipstick.
أحمر شفاه
Next episode's case is really unique.
!قضيّة الحلقة القادمة فريدة
Do you think I'm pretty?
أأنا جميل؟